  <data name="SystemDesign_RequestFlowTitle" xml:space="preserve">
    <value>🌐  Request Flow</value>
  </data>
  <data name="SystemDesign_RequestFlowDesc1" xml:space="preserve">
    <value>All traffic enters through an AWS Application Load Balancer. HTTP :80 is automatically redirected to HTTPS :443; TLS is terminated at the ALB using an ACM-managed certificate covering both doggerbank.online and www.doggerbank.online.</value>
  </data>
  <data name="SystemDesign_RequestFlowDesc2" xml:space="preserve">
    <value>The ALB forwards requests to the web-client service, which is backed by three or more nginx pods. Static assets (the Uno WASM bundle, fonts, images) are served directly from nginx. API calls — any path matching /api/* — are proxied upstream to the api Kubernetes service on port 8282.</value>
  </data>
  <data name="SystemDesign_FrontendTitle" xml:space="preserve">
    <value>🖥️  Frontend — Uno Platform WebAssembly</value>
  </data>
  <data name="SystemDesign_FrontendDesc1" xml:space="preserve">
    <value>The client is a C# / XAML application compiled to WebAssembly using Uno Platform (net10.0-browserwasm, Skia renderer). The entire application — runtime, fonts, assets — runs inside the browser's WASM sandbox with no server-side rendering.</value>
  </data>
  <data name="SystemDesign_FrontendDesc2" xml:space="preserve">
    <value>nginx serves the WASM bundle with gzip compression. index.html, AppManifest.js and service-worker.js carry no-store cache directives so the browser always fetches the latest version on reload, while the large WASM binary and asset files are cached aggressively by the service worker.</value>
  </data>
  <data name="SystemDesign_FrontendDesc3" xml:space="preserve">
    <value>The API base URL is resolved at runtime from window.location, so the same compiled binary works without modification behind any hostname — local Docker Compose or the cloud ALB.</value>
  </data>
  <data name="SystemDesign_ApiTitle" xml:space="preserve">
    <value>☕  API — Spring Boot 3 · Java 21</value>
  </data>
  <data name="SystemDesign_ApiDesc1" xml:space="preserve">
    <value>The REST API is a Spring Boot 3.5.1 application running on Java 21 with virtual threads enabled for efficient async I/O. It exposes four operations under the /api prefix: factorial, fibonacci, streaming primes (Server-Sent Events), and mathematician of the day.</value>
  </data>
  <data name="SystemDesign_ApiDesc2" xml:space="preserve">
    <value>Persistence uses Spring Data JPA with a HikariCP connection pool (max 10 connections). Primes results are cached in Redis with a 24-hour TTL — cache hits skip all computation and stream directly from the store, making the API stateless and safe to scale horizontally.</value>
  </data>
  <data name="SystemDesign_ApiDesc3" xml:space="preserve">
    <value>Metrics are exposed on /actuator/prometheus via Micrometer with custom counters and timers for each math operation. Structured JSON logs are produced by logstash-logback-encoder. Distributed traces are emitted by the OpenTelemetry Java agent (zero-code instrumentation) to Tempo via OTLP/gRPC on port 4317.</value>
  </data>
